

# Sadaf Bagadia

GDBA(Graduate Diploma in Business Administration)

E-mail: sadaf.bagadia@gmail.com

Mobile: +91 9978133813

Add- 50 Tawakal Villa Society, Nr. Old Bhata School-Juhapura-Ahmedabad-Gujarat.

Linkedin:www.linkedin.com/in/sadafbagadia

### **Summary:**

Skilled professional with experience in recruiting and Staffing, Researching and Sourcing diverse candidates. Successfully delivers results while managing complex and challenging situations. A strong communicator and relationship builder who cultivates authentic business relationships. Loyal, principle-driven professional recognized for positive attitude and impeccable ethics.

### **Experience:**

#### Assistant Manager- Recruitment at Kairos Establishment Services LLP

#### **December 2018 – Present**

- Responsibilities include recruiting candidates of skills for our clients and developing new business for our company and interacting with clients.
- ➤ Worked with a variety of requirements from IT, Healthcare and Telecom and Engineering domain etc.
- Expertise in using sourcing tools like LinkedIn, Google (Basic), Career Builder, and Monster, Naukrietc.
- > Sourcedand Screened candidates resume to the client requirements, to determine the best applicant for the job.
- Negotiated wage rates and benefit packages and other terms and conditions of employment with candidates.
- > Gained commitment from candidates for current and future job requirements.
- Prepared candidates for all job interviews by providing detailed information on the company, the hiring manager, our business strategy, department background, job descriptions, and expectations.
- Guide and helped candidates for interviews and start dates to the client site.
- Worked on a special and niche projects to find out the best talents in IT, Healthcare and Telecom and Engineering domain etc.
- Achieving targets day on day and month on month basis as set by the company with focus on maintaining quality and client satisfaction.

# Sr. Recruitment Consultant at IMS People October 2014 - November 2018 (4 Years and 1 Month)

- Responsibilities include recruiting U.S candidates of skills for our clients.
- Worked with a variety of requirements from IT, Healthcare and Telecom and Engineering domain etc.
- Expertise in using sourcing tools like Linked In, Google, Career Builder, and Monster etc.
- > Sourced and Screened candidates resume to the client requirements, to determine the best applicant

- for the job.
- Negotiated wage rates and benefit packages and other terms and conditions of employment with candidates.
- ➤ Gained commitment from candidates for current and future job requirements.
- Underwent full recruitment life cycle with the candidates.
- Maintained a professional and consistent relationship with the clients/candidates.
- Prepared candidates for all job interviews by providing detailed information on the company, the hiring manage, our business strategy, department background, job descriptions, and expectations.
- Worked on a special and niche projects to find out the best talents in IT, Healthcare and Telecom and Engineering domain etc.
- Prepare detailed Daily, Weekly and Monthly Reports and prepare weekly Synopsis to share with Senior management.
- Keep Track of Daily Work and client's requirements.
- Interact with client daily to get Updates and Feedback. Also, co-ordinate with client for Doubts and queries if any.

## **Process Associate at Ascendum Solutions**

### May 2013 - January 2014

- Responsible for initial audit of mortgage loan application, need to process and work as qualifier of loan documents submitted by the loan applicant.
- Need to verify and check docs like, Bank Statements, TaxStatements, Income Proof, Paystub etc. need to qualify the loan docs following the guidelines set by the clients.

# Easy Transcription & Software Pvt Ltd. Allocation and Back Office Executive April 2010 - August 2012

- Managing Total work load. Handling and managing Vendors pan Indian, also take care of the Targets for the Medical Transcriptionist, QA's and Editors.
- Interacting with US team if needed and preparing daily, weekly and monthly reports.
- > Took care of all allocation work also maintaining and taking care of Chennai officework load and allocating total work to Chennai office.
- Responsible for Vendor Management PAN India Level.

#### **Honors and Awards**

Top Performing Source/Lead Generator-July 2016-IMS People.

#### **Education**

### **National Institute of Management**

Graduate Diploma in Business Administration, Business Administration, 2005 – 2008

#### **General Certification**

IELTS (6.5 Band) 2016 - British Council

# **Ankur High School**

HSC, Accounts, 2003 - 2005

Activities and Societies: Sports, Volley Ball

# **Trinity English School**

SSC, All Subjects, 1989 - 2003

Activities and Societies: Sports team and different cultural committee members.